bookmarks.com 2010-06-11

# netRocket bookmarking, tagging and scheduling the sites you browse and discover -- Privacy Policy

Last Updated December 16, 2007

isend.com, LLC d/b/a NetRocket (“NetRocket”) collects, receives and uses information, including personal information and information concerning your past use of the NetRocket web site(s), its products and its services. Personal information is identifying information such as your name, age, address, email address, and telephone phone number. At present, the only personal information collected by NetRocket is a user’s email address. Personal information does not include information such as usage or other demographic information when that information does not contain identifying information. 

NetRocket has business, and will have relationships with other commercial entities, and NetRocket does not control third parties or their respective privacy policies. 

How NetRocket collects information

NetRocket collects information, including your personal information: 

  * when you register as a user with NetRocket
  * when you use NetRocket products or services
  * when you use the NetRocket web site(s)
  * when you use our partners’ and affiliates web sites, if any
  * and when you participate in promotions, which may be offered by NetRocket from time to time. 

NetRocket may aggregate your information with other information, including other personal information, that we may receive from third parties or from your use of our website(s). 

NetRocket requires certain information when you register as a user at our web site(s), for example, your username, email address, password and your time zone (e.g. EST, MST, etc.). NetRocket may ask, from time to time, though it has no specific, present plans to do so, for certain demographic information such as your age, occupation, industry, and personal interests. NetRocket may also require certain personal information to be used for security purposes. Personal information collected solely for security purposes will never be shared with any person or entity, but shall only be used to authenticate you to our web site(s). 

NetRocket may collect information about your transactions with us as well as those with our business partners and affiliates, NetRocket uses all manner of technology to set, access, and collect information, including transparent images, web beacons, and other scripts. 

NetRocket collects information on our server logs from your browser, including your IP address, NetRocket cookies, referring pages and web sites, and the page you request, among other information. NetRocket shall never share its originating cookie information with any third party, except as provided below. 

How NetRocket uses personal information

NetRocket currently uses personal information it collects and receives solely to administer your user account and enhance your user experience at our web sites. NetRocket currently uses user usage information, including the identity of bookmarked websites, in aggregated form only, as part of its service offerings to all users. In the future, NetRocket may use personal information it collects and receives to direct content you see, including advertisements; to fulfill your requests for products and services; to improve our web site(s), products and services; to conduct research; and to provide anonymous reporting for all purposes. NetRocket may also use the information it collects to contact you, or as otherwise provided in this document. 

How NetRocket shares information

NetRocket does not rent, sell, or share personal information about you with other people or non-affiliated companies except to provide products or services you’ve requested, or as provided below. 

  * NetRocket may share information, including personal information with our business partners and/or affiliates, but only pursuant to confidentiality agreements which provide that your personal information shall be deemed confidential.
  * NetRocket may share information, including personal information to comply with subpoenas, court orders, or other as otherwise required by law or to exercise our legal rights.
  * NetRocket will share information, including personal information (and cookies) in the event of a sale, merger, or other organic change to the corporate structure if NetRocket, or as part of a sale of our assets.
  * NetRocket will share user usage information with third parties, including other users, but only in aggregated, not personally identifying, form.

How NetRocket uses security-related information

NetRocket uses security-related information only for the purpose of authentication. This information may be used to authenticate you to our servers and our employees. This information is not used for any other purpose. Only those employees that reasonably require access to security-related information may see it. No employee will ever ask for, or be able to see your password. 

How NetRocket makes changes to its Privacy Policy

NetRocket may modify or update this policy at any time. We will notify you about major changes to this policy as such changes affect the use of your personal information. NetRocket shall notify you by sending such notices to the email address specified in your NetRocket account and/or by placing a notice on our site. Consequently, you agree to regularly visit the NetRocket web sites so that you will be kept informed of any changes to this privacy policy or any other policy or terms governing your use of the NetRocket web sites, products or services.
